const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Which sahaba did Prophet Muhammad (ﷺ) help to become free from being a slave by planting 300+ date palm trees?",
    options: [
      "Bilal ibn Rabah (ra)",
      "Thawban ibn Bujdud (ra)",
      "Salman al Farisi (ra)",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "What is the virtue of reciting Ayatul Kursi before going to bed at night to sleep?",
    options: [
      "Takes away hunger",
      "Gives you strength",
      "You are protected from harm till sunrise",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which Prophet (as) had control of the Jinn and was able to talk to animals?",
    options: ["Sulaiman (as)", "Dawud (as)", "Yunus (as)"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What does Zam Zam mean?",
    options: ["Holy water", "Water well", "Stop "],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is Az-Zaqqum?",
    options: [
      "Food for the people of hellfire",
      "Drink for the people of hellfire",
      "Home for the people of hellfire",
    ],
    answer: 0,
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not an example of Major Shirk?",
    options: [
      "Asking help from a Prophet",
      "Going to a pious person’s grave for blessings",
      "Showing off",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What does Allah’s name Al-Mu’izz mean?",
    options: [
      "The One who dishonours",
      "The One who honours",
      "The One who will judge",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Who was a first cousin of Prophet Muhammad (peace be upon him)?",
    options: [
      "Abdullah ibn al-Abbas (ra)",
      "Abdullah ibn Umar (ra)",
      "Khalid ibn Waleed (ra)",
    ],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Who will get their book of deeds in the right hand on the Day of Judgment?",
    options: ["The disbelievers", "The believers", "The hypocrites"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "What issue was Imam al-Bukhari (rh) born with and how as it fixed?",
    options: [
      "Deaf & fixed with medicine",
      "Deaf & fixed with mother’s dua",
      "Blind & fixed with mother’s dua",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
];

export default questions;
